Finding Aid for Carol June Bradley Music Librarianship Oral History Recordings, 1973-1988
State University of New York at Buffalo. Music Library
- Cassettes, 1973-1988, I.; Cassette 1-135
  - Spivacke, Harold, 1904-1977: Part 3, 1974-04-10, 1 audiocassette; Duration: 00:28:21 Location of recording: Washington (D.C.) Type of tape: TDK C-60LN stereo. Side 2 is blank. (Box 3, Audiocassette 113)
    Preservation archival master files: ubmu0076_113_01_am.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0076_113_01_sc.mp3
  - Spivacke, Harold, 1904-1977: Part 4, 1974-04-10, 1 audiocassette; Duration: 01:01:54 Location of recording: Washington (D.C.) Type of tape: TDK C-60LN mono. (Box 3, Audiocassette 114)
    Preservation archival master files: ubmu0076_114_01_am.wav, ubmu0076_114_02_am.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0076_114_01_sc.mp3, ubmu0076_114_02_sc.mp3
  - Spivacke, Harold, 1904-1977: Part 5, 1974-04-10--1974-04-11, 1 audiocassette; Duration: 01:02:24 Location of recording: Washington (D.C.) Type of tape: TDK D C60 mono. (Box 3, Audiocassette 115)
    Preservation archival master files: ubmu0076_115_01_am.wav, ubmu0076_115_02_am.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0076_115_01_sc.mp3, ubmu0076_115_02_sc.mp3
  - Spivacke, Harold, 1904-1977: Part 6, 1974-04-11, 1 audiocassette; Duration: 01:00:31 Location of recording: Washington (D.C.) Type of tape: TDK D C60 stereo. (Box 3, Audiocassette 116)
    Preservation archival master files: ubmu0076_116_01_am.wav, ubmu0076_116_02_am.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0076_116_01_sc.mp3, ubmu0076_116_02_sc.mp3
  - Spivacke, Harold, 1904-1977: Part 7, 1974-04-11, 1 audiocassette; Duration: 00:24:27 Location of recording: Washington (D.C.) Type of tape: TDK D C60 mono. Side 2 is blank. (Box 3, Audiocassette 117)
    Preservation archival master files: ubmu0076_117_01_am.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0076_117_01_sc.mp3
  - Watanabe, Ruth T. (Ruth Taiko): Part 1, 1984-10-31, 1 audiocassette; Duration: 01:02:42 Location of recording: Rochester (N.Y.) Type of tape: Maxell UDXLII 60 mono. (Box 3, Audiocassette 118)
    Preservation archival master files: ubmu0076_118_01_am.wav, ubmu0076_118_02_am.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0076_118_01_sc.mp3, ubmu0076_118_02_sc.mp3
  - Watanabe, Ruth T. (Ruth Taiko): Part 2, 1984-10-31, 1 audiocassette; Duration: 01:00:10 Location of recording: Rochester (N.Y.) Type of tape: Maxell UDXLII 60 mono. (Box 3, Audiocassette 119)
    Preservation archival master files: ubmu0076_119_01_am.wav, ubmu0076_119_02_am.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0076_119_01_sc.mp3, ubmu0076_119_02_sc.mp3
  - Watanabe, Ruth T. (Ruth Taiko): Part 3, 1984-10-31, 1 audiocassette; Duration: 00:47:09 Location of recording: Rochester (N.Y.) Type of tape: Maxell UDXLII 60 mono. (Box 3, Audiocassette 120)
    Preservation archival master files: ubmu0076_120_01_am.wav, ubmu0076_120_02_am.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0076_120_01_sc.mp3, ubmu0076_120_02_sc.mp3
  - Watanabe, Ruth T. (Ruth Taiko): Part 4, 1984-11-10, 1 audiocassette; Duration: 01:03:26 Location of recording: Rochester (N.Y.) Type of tape: Maxell UDXLII 60 mono. (Box 3, Audiocassette 121)
    Preservation archival master files: ubmu0076_121_01_am.wav, ubmu0076_121_02_am.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0076_121_01_sc.mp3, ubmu0076_121_02_sc.mp3
  - Watanabe, Ruth T. (Ruth Taiko): Part 5, 1984-11-10, 1 audiocassette; Duration: 01:00:02 Location of recording: Rochester (N.Y.) Type of tape: Maxell UDXLII 60 mono. (Box 3, Audiocassette 122)
    Preservation archival master files: ubmu0076_122_01_am.wav, ubmu0076_122_02_am.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0076_122_01_sc.mp3, ubmu0076_122_02_sc.mp3
  - Watanabe, Ruth T. (Ruth Taiko): Part 6, 1984-11-10, 1 audiocassette; Duration: 00:54:47 Location of recording: Rochester (N.Y.) Type of tape: Maxell UDXLII 60 mono. (Box 3, Audiocassette 123)
    Preservation archival master files: ubmu0076_123_01_am.wav, ubmu0076_123_02_am.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0076_123_01_sc.mp3, ubmu0076_123_02_sc.mp3
  - Watanabe, Ruth T. (Ruth Taiko): Part 7, 1984-12-01, 1 audiocassette; Duration: 00:57:27 Location of recording: Rochester (N.Y.) Type of tape: Maxell UDXLII 60 mono. (Box 3, Audiocassette 124)
    Preservation archival master files: ubmu0076_124_01_am.wav, ubmu0076_124_02_am.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0076_124_01_sc.mp3, ubmu0076_124_02_sc.mp3
  - Watanabe, Ruth T. (Ruth Taiko): Part 8, 1984-12-01, 1 audiocassette; Duration: 00:59:00 Location of recording: Rochester (N.Y.) Type of tape: Maxell UDXLII 60 mono. (Box 3, Audiocassette 125)
    Preservation archival master files: ubmu0076_125_01_am.wav, ubmu0076_125_02_am.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0076_125_01_sc.mp3, ubmu0076_125_02_sc.mp3
  - Watanabe, Ruth T. (Ruth Taiko): Part 9, 1984-12-01, 1 audiocassette; Duration: 00:44:25 Location of recording: Rochester (N.Y.) Type of tape: Maxell UDXLII 60 mono. (Box 3, Audiocassette 126)
    Preservation archival master files: ubmu0076_126_01_am.wav, ubmu0076_126_02_am.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0076_126_01_sc.mp3, ubmu0076_126_02_sc.mp3
  - Waters, Edward N. (Edward Neighbor), 1906-1991: Part 1, 1978-01-03, 1 audiocassette; Duration: 01:01:18 Location of recording: Washington (D.C.) Type of tape: Realistic C-60 stereo. (Box 3, Audiocassette 127)
    Preservation archival master files: ubmu0076_127_01_am.wav, ubmu0076_127_02_am.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0076_127_01_sc.mp3, ubmu0076_127_02_sc.mp3
  - Waters, Edward N. (Edward Neighbor), 1906-1991: Part 2, 1978-01-03, 1 audiocassette; Duration: 01:02:32 Location of recording: Washington (D.C.) Type of tape: Realistic C-60 stereo. (Box 3, Audiocassette 128)
    Preservation archival master files: ubmu0076_128_01_am.wav, ubmu0076_128_02_am.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0076_128_01_sc.mp3, ubmu0076_128_02_sc.mp3
  - Waters, Edward N. (Edward Neighbor), 1906-1991: Part 3, 1978-01-03, 1 audiocassette; Duration: 00:52:38 Location of recording: Washington (D.C.) Type of tape: Realistic C-60 stereo. (Box 3, Audiocassette 129)
    Preservation archival master files: ubmu0076_129_01_am.wav, ubmu0076_129_02_am.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0076_129_01_sc.mp3, ubmu0076_129_02_sc.mp3
  - Waters, Edward N. (Edward Neighbor), 1906-1991: Part 4, 1979-01-05, 1 audiocassette; Duration: 00:58:45 Location of recording: Washington (D.C.) Type of tape: Maxell UDXLII C60 stereo. Marked "Conversational, private" (Box 3, Audiocassette 130)
    Preservation archival master files: ubmu0076_130_01_am.wav, ubmu0076_130_02_am.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0076_130_01_sc.mp3, ubmu0076_130_02_sc.mp3
  - Weichlein, William J. (William Jesset), 1917-1988: Part 1, 1985-12-13, 1 audiocassette; Duration: 01:02:47 Location of recording: Ann Arbor (Mich.) Type of tape: Maxell UDXLII 60 stereo. Copyright and literary rights belong to the Music Library Association (Box 3, Audiocassette 131)
    Preservation archival master files: ubmu0076_131_01_am.wav, ubmu0076_131_02_am.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0076_131_01_sc.mp3, ubmu0076_131_02_sc.mp3
  - Weichlein, William J. (William Jesset), 1917-1988: Part 2, 1985-12-13--1985-12-14, 1 audiocassette; Duration: 00:37:38 Location of recording: Ann Arbor (Mich.) Type of tape: Maxell UDXLII 60 stereo. Copyright and literary rights belong to the Music Library Association (Box 3, Audiocassette 132)
    Preservation archival master files: ubmu0076_132_01_am.wav, ubmu0076_132_02_am.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0076_132_01_sc.mp3, ubmu0076_132_02_sc.mp3
  - Weichlein, William J. (William Jesset), 1917-1988: Part 3, 1985-12-14, 1 audiocassette; Duration: 00:56:47 Location of recording: Ann Arbor (Mich.) Type of tape: Maxell UDXLII 60 stereo. Copyright and literary rights belong to the Music Library Association (Box 3, Audiocassette 133)
    Preservation archival master files: ubmu0076_133_01_am.wav, ubmu0076_133_02_am.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0076_133_01_sc.mp3, ubmu0076_133_02_sc.mp3
  - Weichlein, William J. (William Jesset), 1917-1988: Part 4, 1985-12-14--1985-12-15, 1 audiocassette; Duration: 00:56:57 Location of recording: Ann Arbor (Mich.) Type of tape: Maxell UDXLII 60 stereo. Copyright and literary rights belong to the Music Library Association (Box 3, Audiocassette 134)
    Preservation archival master files: ubmu0076_134_01_am.wav, ubmu0076_134_02_am.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0076_134_01_sc.mp3, ubmu0076_134_02_sc.mp3
  - Weichlein, William J. (William Jesset), 1917-1988: Part 5, 1985-12-15, 1 audiocassette; Duration: 00:26:36 Location of recording: Ann Arbor (Mich.) Type of tape: Maxell UDXLII 60 stereo. Side 2 is blank. Copyright and literary rights belong to the Music Library Association (Box 3, Audiocassette 135)
    Preservation archival master files: ubmu0076_135_01_am.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0076_135_01_sc.mp3
Search Terms
The following terms have been used to index the description of this collection in the Library's online catalog.
Subjects
Music librarians--Interviews; Music librarianship -- United States -- 20th century
Genres
audiocassettes; oral histories (document genres)